<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-06-30T19:40:48-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">Drink in the Data</title><subtitle>Drink in the data Or Drinkin' the data, is a Data science blog. The goal will be to create cool shit with ugly data. Its gonna be sick, follow the site and check out the cool posts. If you have some data and you think its interesting send it to us and it might be used in one the posts.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">So I needed a way to put ‘Data Science’ On my resume</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/06/30/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="So I needed a way to put 'Data Science' On my resume" /><published>2018-06-30T19:06:10-07:00</published><updated>2018-06-30T19:06:10-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/06/30/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/06/30/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;You heard it right from the source. I want a good job and I want it to use Data science. So how do i do that?
I make a blog and I use it to show case my mad hacker skillz. These hands were made to plug shit into R. so lets gooooooooo.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">You heard it right from the source. I want a good job and I want it to use Data science. So how do i do that? I make a blog and I use it to show case my mad hacker skillz. These hands were made to plug shit into R. so lets gooooooooo.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cross Country analysis</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/06/20/Cross-Country.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cross Country analysis" /><published>2018-06-20T19:06:10-07:00</published><updated>2018-06-20T19:06:10-07:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/06/20/Cross-Country</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2018/06/20/Cross-Country.html">&lt;p&gt;So here is the data for from the last 10 years on cross country races for Washington state.
THe data was pulled from athletic.net using by hand and entered into Excel. The excel file was then
loaded into R-SHiny and is hosted using their free tier hosting. you will need to click the pictures to move to the website.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">So here is the data for from the last 10 years on cross country races for Washington state. THe data was pulled from athletic.net using by hand and entered into Excel. The excel file was then loaded into R-SHiny and is hosted using their free tier hosting. you will need to click the pictures to move to the website.</summary></entry></feed>